cdburnerxp.se 2015-11-27

# CDBurnerXP: Privacy Policy

If you contact us using the contact form (at <http://cdburnerxp.se/contact>), only the data you entered in one of the fields will be stored. 

The information you submitted will not be shared with third parties, but only used to answer your request by those who received it. 

## Error reports

If you encounter an error while using CDBurnerXP, and you decide an to send us an error report, _only_ the following information will be submitted: 

  * The name and version of your operating system

  * The error message, the stack strace and a list of all installed devices, as shown in the dialog

  * If you let the option enabled, a screenshot of the screen's content just before the error report dialog opened

  * Your e-mail address and description of the problem if you enter it

  * The version number of CDBurnerXP (as shown in the about dialog)

The received data will solely be used in attempt to solve your problem with CDBurnerXP. The information will not be shared with third parties, except for developers of third party components used in CDBurnerXP if it is required in order to fix the problem. 

## Working devices

If you submit a working drive, we collect the following information _only_ : 

  * Device vendor as shown in the dialog

  * Device model as shown in the dialog

  * Device type as shown in the dialog

  * The version number of CDBurnerXP (as shown in the about dialog)

Further system or personal information is **not** being submitted or stored. The submitted data is then publicly visible at <http://cdburnerxp.se/testeddrives>. 

## Usage of Cookies

Cookies will be used to store a user's settings (like login information at the [forum](http://forum.cdburnerxp.se/ "http://forum.cdburnerxp.se") or the preferred website language). No personal information is stored within them.   
Additional to that, third parties which are not under our control may use cookies. Google for example uses cookies for ads displayed on the web page, and they have their own [privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy.html "http://www.google.com/privacy.html"). 

Note about Google ads: Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads based on your visit to this site and other sites on the Internet. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html "http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html"). 

## Echo Nest music identification

For music identification (if you use the feature), CDBurnerXP generates a fingerprint of the song you identify (basically a “compressed” version of the music that only is a few KB in size) and submits it to EchoNest servers. No further data that identifies yourself or your file is submitted. 

You may also want to check the [EchoNest privacy policy](http://the.echonest.com/privacy/ "http://the.echonest.com/privacy/"). 

## Installer / OpenCandy

The default installer (there are also setup packages without included) makes use of the OpenCandy advertisement platform. When installing CDBurnerXP, you are asked to accept the OpenCandy EULA as following: 

This installer uses the OpenCandy network to recommend other software you may find valuable during the installation of this software. OpenCandy collects *NON-personally identifiable* information about this installation and the recommendation process. Collection of this information ONLY occurs during this installation and the recommendation process; in accordance with OpenCandy's Privacy Policy, available at [www.opencandy.com/privacy-policy](http://www.opencandy.com/privacy-policy "http://www.opencandy.com/privacy-policy")

More information about the collected data can also be found on [Your Privacy and The OpenCandy Network](http://www.opencandy.com/privacy-matters/opencandy-network-details/ "http://www.opencandy.com/privacy-matters/opencandy-network-details/").
